Hi.
Alright, before we start with our eggplant, beautiful eggplant by the way, make sure you lower that flame and just let that simmer.
That paste and that garlic.
And while that's simmering now we're going to start to chop this beautiful eggplant.
Alright the first thing you're going to do is chop off the end of the stem where the top is of the eggplant.
To get a beautiful eggplant, make sure they're, get a beautiful eggplant make sure they're not bruised anywhere, they're firm to the touch.
Listen to that.
You can hear it, it's nice and firm.
Beautiful.
And what we're going to do is cut off both ends.
What I like to do is real simple.
Just cut it in half.
Make sure you wash your veggies really good.
Alright?
What I do is just cut this bad boy in half.
Put the flat side down.
I'll cut it in half again, like so.
I'll do the same thing to the other one.
Now this was a big sized eggplant.
So what I'm going to do now is just coming back, make it like one inch pieces.
This is such a big eggplant, I'm actually going to slice it again here, just to make the cubes more symmetrical.
Remember what I'm going to do is just cut about an inch back.
And you'll see, you'll have nice size pieces that way.
And like I said, this is going to cook down. There's a lot of water in this. I'm going to try to get all of that flavors of this beautiful eggplant.
Eggplant is, I tell you it's delicious and it's good for you.
So again if you have some big pieces like this, you might want to cut this down too.